All right.
好的。
We're getting close to the end of our lesson on quanta fires and we're going to look at now three which
我们即将结束关于量子火灾的课程，现在我们将看看其中的三个
are used only for countable nouns.
仅用于可数名词。
A couple a few and several.
几个几个。
And actually they're very similar.
实际上它们非常相似。
Let's just talk very quickly about the differences between them.
让我们快速谈谈它们之间的差异。
A couple is generally too although sometimes people use it to say three.
一对通常也是，尽管有时人们用它来表示三个。
It's just something that kind of becomes a habit for some people.
对于某些人来说，这只是一种习惯。
A few is more than two but not many.
几个多于两个，但不多。
It's usually a small number of.
它通常是少数。
And some people again might use it for two out of habit.
有些人可能会出于习惯再次将其用于两个。
But generally speaking it just means not many.
但一般来说，它只是意味着不多。
And then several is more than two but not many more than two but not many.
然后几个多于二，但不多于二，但不多。
And again sometimes sometimes you might hear people use it for two but definitely not one definitely
有时，有时您可能会听到人们将它用于两个，但绝对不是一个
not one.
不是一个。
And this can be very you know a wide range because a few could be a hundred at the small end of a very
这可能是你知道的范围很广，因为在一个非常小的范围内，少数可能是一百个
large scale if the scale is on this and 10 billion.
如果规模在这个和100亿之间，规模很大。
And on this end a hundred.
并在此结束一百。
Well some people might say then a hundred is a few.
好吧，有些人可能会说一百是几个。
So there are some there are some good interesting examples where a few is actually a lot compared to
所以有一些很好的有趣的例子，其中一些实际上很多
one.
一。
Generally that's not the case.
通常情况并非如此。
Generally it's three four five maybe six.
一般是三四五或者六。
That's how it's usually used.
这就是它通常的使用方式。
But I just want to show you that it is possible in some cases to use it as a much larger number.
但我只是想告诉你，在某些情况下可以将它用作更大的数字。
Several several OK several is usually three four sometimes five.
几个几个OK几个通常是三四有时五。
Usually around there.
一般都在附近。
But it's it's not too it's not too.
但它不是太它不是太。
Let's actually go through some examples of these simple words and phrases.
让我们来看看这些简单的单词和短语的一些例子。
It takes a couple weeks to process applications to an application is something that you need to maybe
处理应用程序的应用程序需要几个星期，这可能是您需要的
fill in if you're going to get a bank account or maybe apply for a job or a visa.
如果您要获得银行账户或申请工作或签证，请填写。
And it has steps a process has steps but process here is a verb to process something.
它有步骤，过程有步骤，但这里的过程是处理某事的动词。
So it takes several weeks to process.
所以需要几周的时间来处理。
That means they need to review it and check it before they give you a result.
这意味着他们需要在给您结果之前对其进行审查和检查。
It takes a couple weeks.
这需要几个星期。
Means it takes probably two weeks or around there.
意味着可能需要两周或大约两周的时间。
It doesn't mean exactly 14 days maybe 13 maybe 15.
这并不意味着正好是 14 天，也许是 13 天，也许是 15 天。
If you want to put in usually here you could.
如果你想通常放在这里，你可以。
It usually takes a couple weeks to process applications.
处理申请通常需要几周时间。
OK.
好的。
I need a few minutes to calm down a few minutes to calm down.
我需要几分钟冷静下来几分钟冷静下来。
Something crazy happens.
疯狂的事情发生了。
I've stressed I've been fired or whatever and someone says Hey are you OK.
我已经强调我被解雇了或其他什么，有人说嘿，你还好吗。
And I go Oh yeah give me a few minutes to calm down so calming down is what we do after something exciting
我走了哦，是的，给我几分钟冷静下来，所以冷静下来是我们在激动人心的事情之后所做的事情
happens that makes us feel stressed.
发生让我们感到压力的事情。
We feel stressed we need to calm down.
我们感到压力很大，需要冷静下来。
And it might take us three four five six minutes to do that.
我们可能需要三四五六分钟才能做到这一点。
Take a few aspirin.
吃几片阿司匹林。
OK.
好的。
Aspirin is something that we take for pain relief when to relieve pain and we would take two or three
阿司匹林是我们用来缓解疼痛的东西，当缓解疼痛时，我们会服用两到三个
or four of those depending on maybe our age.
或其中四个取决于我们的年龄。
I'm not giving you medical advice here.
我不是在这里给你医疗建议。
Check the bottle.
检查瓶子。
OK.
好的。
After several reminders he was fired several three maybe four OK maybe five reminders are basically
经过几次提醒他被解雇了几个三也许四OK也许五提醒基本上是
times when he did something bad he was late on Monday and then he was late the next month on Thursday
有时他做坏事时周一迟到，然后下个月周四迟到
and the next month it was late on Wednesday and he was given two reminders and then given a final reminder
下个月星期三晚了给了他两次提醒，然后给了最后一次提醒
and then he was fired don't be late Don't be late Don't be late you're fired.
然后他被解雇了 不要迟到 不要迟到 不要迟到 你被解雇了。
Those three are reminders and several is to give you a feeling for the number.
这三个是提醒，有几个是为了给你一个数字的感觉。
Why don't we just say the number why don't we say he was given three reminders.
我们为什么不直接说数字为什么不说他收到了三个提醒。
Well take three aspirin.
吃三颗阿司匹林就好了。
We could we could but I feel it makes the world very stiff when we give specific numbers and in life
我们可以，但我觉得当我们给出具体的数字和生活时，这会让世界变得非常僵硬
we don't always know exact numbers.
我们并不总是知道确切的数字。
Right.
正确的。
We often want to give a general idea and we have no idea what the specific number is.
我们经常想给出一个大致的概念，我们不知道具体的数字是多少。
So that's why quantum fires are so useful.
这就是为什么量子火焰如此有用的原因。
That's why quantum fires help us to express quantities or amounts and not be locked into being wrong
这就是为什么量子火可以帮助我们表达数量或数量，而不是被锁定在错误中
because we gave the wrong number.
因为我们给错了号码。
Right.
正确的。
So it's actually extremely useful and you need to know how to use them very naturally.
所以它实际上非常有用，你需要知道如何非常自然地使用它们。